

Objective

A creative, resourceful and ambitious web professional with 6+ years' experience in designing and coding for the web. Seeking to apply those skills and improve every day in order to create quality products, grow as a professional, and provide great service to clients.

Experience

Senior Front-End Developer @ Pool.Garden

5/2021 - Present

Chia Cryptocurrency Farming Pool

Designed UI for a Chia crypto currency farming pool. Developed the front end using Next.js and working in coordination with DevOps engineer to maintain a crypto pool service.

Marketing Web Developer @ Firewalls.com

8/2019 - Present

Firewalls Reseller & Service Provider

Built and maintain a Magento 2 ecommerce website. Overseeing 3 developers and contribute to building a Laravel 8 application, using Vue3 for the front end and Docker for dev environment.

Front-End Developer @ BitLoft

8/2016 - 8/2019

Software Development Company

Worked specifically with Laravel 5, assisted in building a customer management tool. Designed and coded wordpress websites and assisted with UX Design and Interaction Design.

Web Designer @ 4Media

2/2015 - 5/2016

Web & Media Agency

Built various mobile responsive websites using tools like bootstrap and LESS for local and international clients.

Graphic Designer @ JC Marketing

7/2014 - 8/2016 (Freelance, Part Time)

Social Media Company

Worked remotely to provide social media graphics and web design consulting.

Education

BA, Visual Effects & Motion Graphics

2009-2012

The Art Institute Of Fort Lauderdale.

About Me

√ N/A

robertkregloh.com

Technologies

NextJS, Vue3, HTML, CSS, SCSS, LESS, JavaScript, jQuery, Flexbox, CSS Grid, Laravel 8, Docker.

Languages

English, Spanish

Skills

Responsive Web Design, User Experience, Front End Development, Interaction Design, Frameworks, Version Control, Testing and Debugging, Browser Developer Tools. Command Line, Video Editing, Prototyping, Planning, Story Mapping

Tools

Adobe Suite, Sublime Text, GIT, Jira, VS Code, Wordpress CMS, Laravel, Lumen, Bootstrap, Google Cloud Platform, Trello

Methods

Agile/Scrum, Kanban